<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>
<title>Your RSS Feed Title</title>
<description>A brief description of your RSS feed.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<link>http://yourwebsite.com/rss.xml</link>
<atom:link href="http://yourwebsite.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

<!-- LB -->











<item>
<title>the once and future king</title>
<guid>https://desire-direct.comindex.html#the-once-and-future-king</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:48:53 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
<p>
"I suppose that all endeavours which are directed to a purely worldly end, as my famous   
Civilization was, contain within themselves the germs of their own corruption." ~ King Arthur<small>[1]</small>
</p>

<p>
Civilization gazed in awe at the detonation of the Wunderwaffe, triggered by in-organic chain reactions, and mere fortunate circumstances prevented individuals 
to evaporate into shadows of former selves. 
Lightning <i>consciously</i> hits before thunder and 
those who manage the Blitz, succumb to the illusion of advantage over the enemy in the glimpse of anachronistic whig history.
The abundance of anemic belief in the edifice of the world 
and a lack of faith in the unbelievable In /Outside
paves the way for a set future that is anticipated in the past and
supports the ignorance of the fact that the past is manifested in the future. 
The hull of the earth was a gift from god on the condition of <b>one</b> inhuman simple task, 
that of filling an empty vessel with dark humour, earnest weirdness and intelligent naïveté, 
and man indeed, has blown it up.
With grand ambitions to come to know its forbidden causes, 
which are interrelated vertiginous dynamics through time, 
modern man rendered the atmosphere with bricks of reason,
 only to face a flat matrix of meaningless signs, arbitrarily rearranged by alien machines.
 Bourgeois philosophical genealogists like  Freud and Marx
assailed the wonky fortress wall with the canons of critique, 
but unfortunately mortared the partial damage with concrete vocabularies and
extended it with the towers of psychology and economics to secure it even more.
In the heat of missionary zeal they combat fire from below with water from above,
whilst the black sheep of the philosophical family ignites suspicion in the traditional indigenous way.
Hypergeneology, or a "tectonics parading as reasons",<small>[2]</small> as practiced by Nietzsche, 
stands for kindling the general surface by virtue of human impotence 
and shunns the mansplaining of a muddle of causes.
</p>

<p>
Once upon a time, battles between the various kingdoms of philosophy 
had been cultivated and led to in /exclusive showdowns, 
in which questions regarding the What? about life were posed, 
just to be responded in the very same lenghtly certain ambiguity.
The father of the Round Table, who enjoyed a good education and sceptic of that non-sense, 
brought fresh ideas to the tilting ground.
He was an opponent of 'Might is Right' and actively proposed 'Might for Right',
a new politics of good intentions to protect the overall populace from homemade violence, 
rather than staging spectacles in the interest of the privileged.
Although the Wart was taught, that mere speculations on, and faith in,
heavyweight timely matters make magicians immortal,
he could not resist to institutionalize medieval life. 
The castle in the air initially boomed and turned into a rock solid fortress, 
but over time reached the state of stalemate, 
and olde Arthur had to realize with regret, 
that thoughtfully mapped out ethics had buried primal moral code in fertile mud.
His wicked followers, post-fashioned knights with exorbitant plumes on their helmets, 
bored by a timeworn idea of chivalry and too comfy to go on unreasonable quests, 
want to objectively know, how objects work in order to exert their dark science, 
with the objective of preserving Camelot 
as <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2401.05566.pdf?utm_source=substack&utm_medium=email" target="_blank">foul</a> as it is.
Thou invoked by a gnawing anger with the worlde
and an unjust feel of entitlement to enrich thyself, exploiting the many loopholes of justice.
Ye envious ill-bred heirs with Cornwall ties, which root deep down to the Old Ones,
thou slayed thee not by confrontional playful jousting, 
but with the sharpened dagger of modern rationale in the back!
Thou reinforced thine unfounded rumours with sham scientific proof,
that a king's speech is worthless gibberish without any practical use for life! Ye practical, exploiting and gaining profit from the given plethora without returning any value. Checkmate!
</p>

<p>
You see wonderful philosophical alchemy is actually cooked up at the gravitational centre of 
how to fuse miscellaneous matters into precious language, 
which must produce in itself a contradiction to avoid objection.
Such interpolations are always in anticipation, yet in defence of grim spells from brighter space. 
By means of revolutionary logic all metaphysics is verified "Scheinsprache", 
which merely resembles language, argues Rudolf Carnap, member of the inner Vienna Circle, 
for whom language is nothing but vocabulary and syntax. 
In his radical countermove, he endorses formal correct but
crooked sentences, which, according to the logician,
can be put to practical use, that is a sorting into true or false,<small>[3]</small>
hence the result is an envelopment of both values.
This <i>Aufbau</i> of pure logic laid the plane of immanent chaos,
since possibilities are endless and thus unpredictable.
Carnap insists on a definite traditional language with words of single connotation,<small>[4]</small>
typical for pre-historic machinic code, that is willingly copied 
without any understanding as long as it works, such as a function of a bash script in a shell.
According to that, it appears that any term clouded by the atmosphere of thought is a "Scheinbegriff", <i>bEGRIFf</i> in itself however, comes with a tactile notion.
</p>

<p>Notes</p>
[1] White, 488, 2015.<br>
[2] Moynihan, 5-6, 2016.<br>
[3] Carnap, 8, 2022.<br>
[4] Ibid., 10.<br>

<p>References</p>
Carnap, Rudolf. <i>Überwindung der Metaphysik durch logische Analyse der Sprache</i>. Ditzingen: Reclam, 2022.<br>
Fuller, Matthew. <i>Behind the Blip - Essays on the Culture of Software</i>. Brooklyn, NY: Autonomedia, 2003.<br>
Garton, Vincent. <a href="https://www.urbanomic.com/document/language-inhuman/"><i>Language Inhuman</i></a>. Urbanomic, 2023.<br>
Konior, Bogna. <a href="https://www.chaosmotics.com/en/featured/the-impersonal-within-us" target="_blank"><i>The Impersonal Within Us - A conversation with Bogna Konior</i></a>. Chaosmotics, 2022.<br>
Mach, Ernst. <i>Beiträge zur Analyse der Empfindungen</i>. Jena: Verlag von Gustav Fischer, 1886.<br>
McLuhan, Marshall. <i>Visual and Acoustic Space</i>. In Interactive Media: Critical Theory Course Reader Autumn 2012, edited by Centre for Cultural Studies. London, UK: Goldsmiths, 2012/13.<br>
Moynihan, Thomas. <i>Spinal Catastrophism - A Secret History</i>. Falmouth, UK: Urbanomic, 2019.<br>
Negarestani, Reza. <i>Intelligence and Spirit</i>. Falmouth, UK: Urbanomic, 2018.<br> 
Negarestani, Reza. <i><a href="https://youtu.be/xbbZTUjJt68?si=VJ8PMPx_ppIstS5d" target="_blank">ChatGPT, Language and The Future of Thinking & Writing</a></i>. YouTube, 22:08 to 35:38, 2023.<br>
White, T. H. <i>The Once and Future King</i>. London: Harper Voyager, 2015.
]]></description>
</item>










<item>
<title></title>
<guid>https://desire-direct.comindex.html#patternwars01</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:54:48 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
<img src="../images/molecule.gif" style="float: left;">

<p>
Iguanas Inside lush holocene<br>
Icelands<br>
off boundless ant-arctic noösphere<br>
an ocean of Nothingness<br>
fullness yet
</p>

<p>
waves of swirling dust in endless vibration<br>
heated sexual organs devour<br>
fluid vortexes energized<br>
A colossal quantum machine<br> 
simultaneously savouring hole and solid
</p>

<p>
the mingling of monozygotic twins<br>
Darkness and light<br>
essenced into all cosmogenic knowledge,<br>
logs of information in original liquid grey matter<br>
fog of horror, eerie background noise
</p>

<p>
"Using technologies as its organs, man's homeostatic activity has turned him into the master of the Earth; yet he is only powerful in the eyes of an apologist such as himself." ~ Stanisław Lem 
</p>

<p>
The rigorous empirical approach, which implies that
 knowledge originates from immediately given in combination with 
reassembled sensations, 
is commonly thought to be all that man has at his disposal.
But that would be also a definition of a functional but soulless automaton,
which is processing framed patterns of data.
It is true that materialities like blood, ears, eyes, noses and so forth, 
are examined through the very same tools, since the raw materials of nature have been gradually turned into technology and further evolved into excesses like 
microscopes or telescopes to explore, anthropomorphize and colonize the micro- and macrocosmos.
Such systems, which make an appearance to the mind as solid entities,
yet remain mystic black boxes, 
can be described and are somewhat transparent and comprehensible for man.
However, in order to get to grips with boundless matter like noumena or time, 
one must be communicable and take part in 
a wide-ranging debate of many positions and therefore a 
farrago of sensations, involving charlatans
who wholeheartedly practice art, literature and philosophy, 
and argue with an unpleasant language.
Just like the sympton of reason, technology is unconditionally three-fold
with the ability to execute simultaneously good and evil.
On account of the acceleration of communication and transport, it
proceeds on an extra-terrestrial scale, effecting an inflation of space-time.
</p>

<p>
In the meanwhile, the articulation of the body developed into
a dissection within the uttermost atomic ranges,
and scientific interpretation became restricted 
to transform subsurface lively energy into invariant data,
thus feeding the technocapitalist machine,
which in turn has its own alien and hostile dynamics.[1]
The economical model of science stands for
hastily placing descriptions to something difficult to explain
and distrusting inborn ideas or traditions in favour of empirical evidence,
and hence accumulated into oblique and obscure patterns of data.[2]
The new dermis, a tissue of artificial sensors,
wraps patient 0 in an intoxicating, palpably warm, straightjacket,
which was collectively patched up by biopolitics and
subconsciously engineered by the drives of death and mutation.
An accident, as Bratton puts it, that leaves reality in a serious condition,
although a prognosis could be more optimistic if the extensive probing of the in /outside
would lean to more meaning,
and therefore aids the social body's defences, rather than the neoliberal case.[3]
The violent copulation between flesh and technology, eternally constant in the nature of things, 
once effecting the growth of cutting-edge extremities is now severely weakened by recuperation.
The rise of the machines already entails anyway the amputation of the human species as previously imagined, 
and the magnetic heart of gravity combined with rationality, 
will be the decisive actor over life and death of antihuman individualism.[4]
In view of this fact, the 
bias-infected subjects of modern science are focusing on selfish security, 
yet carelessly experimenting with the conversion of the transcendental into objects in stasis.
The deduction from a priori hypotheses represents
a mere two-fold determination of the future by the conformational values of <b>either</b> true /false, however, 
biochemical reaction is inherently de /productive and transformative, without any objective other than essence and thus unpredictable.[5]
</p>

<p>
The skin of the Real is repelling the permeation of endless interrelations and therefore in-sanity, albeit tolerating the harmonic unison of in_outside vibes.
Its suppression promotes mental illness
and self-admitted, surveillanced souls are pushed to make pre-calculated moves in the lunatic asylum, which is bursting at the seams in times of unbearable tension.
And right there, 
where surface phenomena of porous thin skin become visible,
vital molecular exchange is exploited for economic plunder. 
The fatal mixture of internal dread and environmental threat,
deflates into a huge depression, and it comes at no surprise that bipolars 
turn against each other.
And although subconsciously aware of the approaching breakdown, 
the body is 
paralyzed by both over- and understimulation and subjected to chemical reaction.
Evolution is a morphical process in neuronic time
rather than geneological history and
Nietzsche argues, that human activity relentlessly 
serves only one malignant end, that of survival,
for which is no cure as it is ingrown with flesh.
Sanitation is suspicious as it
is futile and destroys any type of germs, 
inclusive of illusive useless links of no purpose,
which are serving the self-regulated, lavish, dirty ()hole, 
home to a manifold, strong but flexible organisms.[6]
</p>

<p>
On a personal note, for this year's spooky season I've (re)watched some of the movies of one of my favourite directors, David Cronenberg. 
I prefer the portrayal of the female as a cold-blooded, mutant monstrosity rather than that of a helpless victim,[7]
which is tried to be fixed but worsened by man-made psycho-physiological technology, as in <i>The Brood</i> (1979) or <i>Dead Ringers</i> (1988). 
The dark humour in <i>The Fly</i> (1986) and <i>Shivers</i> (1975), featuring weirdly cute creatures, addresses the dangers of unbound biotech and indicates
that too much instinctual desire would retransform humans into pre-historic sex machines.
<i>A History of Violence</i> (2005) is, as expected of high quality, an action-packed thriller with sufficient elegant gore, but for me, Cronenberg remains the king of psychological_body_horror. 
</p>

<p>Notes</p>
[1] Mackay, 2014<br>
[2] Negarestani, 2022<br>
[3] Peirano and Bratton, 2021<br>
[4] Negarestani, 2014<br>
[5] Gruppo di Nun, 2022, p. 50<br>
[6] Nietzsche, 1882, p. 23<br>
[7] As in the dramas of Fassbinder and von Trier for example.

<p>References</p>
Ballard, J.G. <i>The Drowned World</i>. London: Fourth Estate, 2014.<br>
Butler, Samuel. <a href="https://en.wikisource.org/wiki/Darwin_among_the_Machines"  target="_blank"><i>Darwin among the Machines</i></a>. 1917.<br>
Gruppo di Nun. <i>Revolutionary Demonology</i>. Falmouth, UK: Urbanomic, 2022.<br>
Lem, Stanisław. <i>Summa Technologiae</i>. Minneapolis, MN: University of Minnesota Press, 2013.<br>
Lyotard, Jean-François. <i>The Inhuman</i>. Stanford, CA: Stanford University Press, 1988.<br>
Mackay, Robin. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tsPOTOLBe4o&t=902s" target="_blank"><i>5 Symposium: Speculations on Anonymous Materials - Robin Mackay</i></a>. YouTube, 2014, 58:25.<br>
Negarestani, Reza. <i>The Labor of the Inhuman, Part II: The Inhuman</i>. e-flux Journal, Issue #53, March 2014.<br>
Negarestani, Reza. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b18nCUTpWDM&t=9845s" target="_blank"><i>Reza Negarestani, Giuseppe Longo, Rocco Gangle, Ian James and Colin McLarty (Philosophy of Science)</i></a>. YouTube, 2022, 2:04:30 to 2:44:05.</br>
Nietzsche, Friedrich. <i>Die fröhliche Wissenschaft</i>. Chemnitz: Verlag von Ernst Schmeitzner, 1882.<br> 
Peirano, Marta. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1jhg-tOPO-s&t=1911s" target="_blank"><i>(re)programming: Infrastructure [Benjamin Bratton]</i></a>. YouTube, 2021, 2:07:57.
]]></description>
</item>






















<item>
<title>Nocturnal Goodness</title>
<guid>https://desire-direct.comindex.html#nocturnal-goodness</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:04:17 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
<img src="../images/nocturnal-goodness.jpg">

<p>
Ho ho ho, a new tarot card for <i>Sounds from the Stone Age</i> dropped!<br>
The painting was inspired by Anti-Oedipus, the trolley problem
and, among many other texts, Gilles Châtelet's 
<i>To Live and Think Like Pigs - The Incitement of Envy and Boredom in Market Democracies</i>.
Prints of cards are out of stock at the moment, but will be available again for non-commercial distribution in spring 2024, watch this space. 
</p>
]]></description>
</item>






<item>
<title></title>
<guid>https://desire-direct.comindex.html#patternwars02</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
<p>
"Life is not consumed by death at its point of greatest depression, but at its peak, and inversely; it is only the brake provided by suffering that preserves the organism in existence." ~ Nick Land
</p>

<p>
The physicist Ernst Mach, predominantly responsible for the work on shock waves, 
also had a share in psychophysics.
He believed, and rightly so, that 
a comprehensive transdisciplinary research would benefit science. 
On the dark side however, beyond an enlightened reality, 
he participated in the great campaign 
towards the inevitable decline and death of Western humankind.
For Mach, <a href="https://publicdomainreview.org/collection/self-portrait-by-ernst-mach-1886/" target="_blank">the view</a> on the whole and the individual
are coherent, however, the from the <i>I</i> imposed role of the 
observer already implies a spin-off from the universal, 
and furthermore, <i>The Analysis of Sensations</i>
is packed with intriguing vague and
contradictory generalizations, 
and therefore features the primary attributes that are
inherent in human and philosophy. 
Time is an intangible spectre, deeply embedded dark matter, 
 and Mach dared to venture into this pit(i)less black hole, 
that with mushrooming tentacles, voraciously gorges on its environment.
And whilst his insides sneaking up behind him,
he tried to explain universal brain phenomena.
What made this natural philosopher so possessed by demons to develop benevolent schizo-paranoia?
Was he infested by a plague, drunk with love, 
incited by the detailed description of the Doppler effect,
where multitonal waves in an ocean of simultaneously nothing and everything,
are sensed in relation to (e)motion in de /progression? 
Maybe none, or even all of it, but we will never know.
</p>

<p>
Early Gestalt psychology was heavily inspired by Mach's contributions,
including the key, mysterious Gestalt-qualität, 
a sort of chemical cohesive, which binds
enlightened thought with the shadowed subconscious.
The bottom-up /top-down approaches of gestaltism,
whereby either the sum of parts, or an immediately
given form, determine 
reality, are both amiss, as subjective sensation is always precarious 
to become a vague quasi-totality, in which coherence is universal. 
And what, if not the sensible soul,
would be ruling this so-called whole anyway?
Mach argues, that the labour of consciousness is likely bound 
to the organic consumption of stimuli, and that the former recognizes time.
The amount of focused effort is in 
relation to the perception of a given moment in time, 
which is literally phrased in German as Lang- /Kurzweile.
His perverted formulation 
certainly makes sense from the cybernetic point of view, where attentive labour is positive, whilst 
wasting valuable life time is negative.[1]
In a similar theory of relativity, Hume distinguishes the resolution of the currently given betwixt Impressions and Ideas, 
depending on the ratio of how forceful and violent it "strikes upon the mind" 
to manifest in thought accordingly.
Impressions produce an instant gratification of pleasure and uneasiness,
affecting the freaky hoggish, propulsive soul straight away and
raise the desire for more and more. 
When the Real runs rampant, 
as in the states of sleep or feverish madness, 
both situated in past traumata, thinking and feeling cuddle up together.
Lesser emotional turmoil, which is formed
not on sight and touch alone and rather converses with active brainwaves, 
replicates most imaginative models that might appear weird but are so much durable in the long term.[2]
The technocapitalist producers of sensational screentime,
<b>mind specialists</b> with a soft spot for the subconscious
and highly skilled in the art of deflexion,
deliberately regulate intense attention towards superficial fun,
then kissing the deadly amused child goodnight and
tucking it to sleep in a designer blanket.
</p>

<p>
Since the becoming of light, cyberwar affects the soul of the biosphere.
Timeless images, captured by the whole body and 
immutably recorded in flesh, are powerful ghosts from the past, 
which signify danger and gave creatures the ability 
to correctly identify un_pleasant crises in a déjà vu with predators.
Actual narratives are compressed in virtual images,
and without remembering each plot twist, it is instinctively known how the story goes.
Lit retrospectives however, are tied to the present by an intellectual string,[3]
probably made up out of very elastic material, 
which is largely expanding the momentum of good old times, and 
possibly a capable cope mechanism in order to suppress inexorable change and death.
Superpowers misappropriate folklore 
by engineering copyrighted, encrypted messages on the conveyer belt,
which are distributed and programmed en masse in 
negative feedback loops to be burnt into collective memory.
In this process,
solely the public key is deployed in 
a one-off asymetric, limited transaction of the monopoly of violence.
Metamyths are surely not deprecated but changed over time and 
captivate through striking individual events, thrown together in 
a nonsensical shifting quantum web, causing utter confusion.
The occurence of fossils of dream memory, which are beyond control of the I 
and go along with hyperarousal,
like goose bumps, flushing and so forth, are intended, 
but lost their original relevant function. 
The fear and loathing of seemingly fast and 
uncoordinated moving small animals, like non-lethal spiders, 
trigger the implulse to kill or seek shelter and
is usually unsubstantiated in a moderate global northern climate.
On the other side however, the terror arising
from seeing the silhouette of birds of prey or hearing the hum of dragonflies,
is completely normal and part of everyday lives. 
</p>

<p>
Land argues in favour of based Kant and critical philosophy
notwithstanding bloated Descartes, who is full of angst and servile to "the whore of reason".
The latter shys away from commitment, although acting pure with modest binary desire,
that directly escalates into utmost bizarre orgies, only to be constrained by the death drive.[4]
But yolo, life is short and tempting and must be lived at its most possible fullest.
The trick is to stay speculative and not fall for prolonged illusions, 
which easily happens if ties of mind and body are severed.
</p>

<p>Notes</p>
[1] Mach, 1886, p. 105<br>
[2] Hume in chapter The Origin of our Ideas, 2003<br>
[3] Mach, 1886, p. 105<br>
[4] Land, 2011, p. 125

<p>References</p>
Fuller, Matthew. <i>How to Sleep. The art, biology and culture of unconsciousness</i>. London, UK: Bloomsbury Academic, 2018.<br> 
Hume, David. <i>A Treatise of Human Nature</i>. Mineola, NY: Dover Publications, 2003.<br>
Land, Nick. <i>Delighted to Death</i>. In <i>Fanged Noumena</i>, edited by Robin Mackay and Ray Brassier. Falmouth, UK: Urbanomic, 2011.<br>
Mach, Ernst. <i>Beiträge zur Analyse der Empfindungen</i>. Jena: Verlag von Gustav Fischer, 1886.<br>
]]></description>
</item>


























































































































<item>
<title>Hello, World!</title>
<guid>https://desire-direct.comindex.html#hello-world</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 15:23:53 +0200</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
<p>
Made a new blog to have a space to get my notes in order and share my research.
Jekyll, which I've used to generate the previous one, got too bloated for my taste.
I wanted to try Luke Smith's 
<a href="https://youtu.be/jIfAdzGmhik?si=uEvw0nMwBrvQxtiT" target="_blank">
lb script</a> for ages, 
so after a fresh Arch install on my recently purchased (refurbished) Lenovo ThinkPad from ebay,
I gave it a shot and forked it. 
I can also recommend Luke's tutorials on old-skool applications like ImageMagick, 
LaTeX or Vim.
</p>

<p>
There is still plenty of customization and tweaking to do, 
but I have much more control and creative freedom than the average platform content creator.
In the process of building a blog nearly from scratch, I get a much better
understanding of what code actually is.
In general I prefer working without a GUI
and navigate the cursor with keys rather than having to grab for the mouse,
which also allows for a faster and seamless writing process.
</p>

<img src="../images/screenshot.jpg">
]]></description>
</item>
































































<p>
Made a new blog to have a space to order my notes and share my research.
Jekyll, which I've used to generate the previous one got too bloated for my taste.
I wanted to try Luke Smith's 
<a href="https://youtu.be/jIfAdzGmhik?si=uEvw0nMwBrvQxtiT">
lb script</a> for ages, 
so after a fresh Arch install on my newly purchased (refurbished) Lenovo ThinkPad from ebay,
I gave it a shot and forked it. 
I can totally recommend Luke's older tutorials on old-skool applications like ImageMagick, 
LateX or Vim.
</p>

<p>
There is still plenty of tweaking and customising to do, 
but I have much more control and creative freedom than the average platform content creator.
In the process of building a blog nearly from scratch, I learn a lot how code works, 
which is usually hidden behind buttons.
</p>


<img src="../images/screenshot.jpg" class="responsive">
]]></description>
</item>


























<p>Made a new blog to build my brand. 
Jekyll, which I've used to generate the old one, got too bloated for my taste. 
I wanted to try Luke Smith's simple and lightweight lb script for ages, 
so I gave it a shot after a fresh Arch install on my new laptop, a refurbished 
Lenovo ThinkPad from ebay.
</p>

<p>There is still plenty of tweaking and customising to do, 
but I have much more control and creative freedom 
than the average platform content creator. 
With building a blog nearly from scratch, I learn a lot how code works, 
which is usually hidden behind buttons.

what is sed
</p>
]]></description>
</item>


















<item>
<title>Options +Indexes
patternwars
test</title>
<guid>https://lukesmith.xyz/2023.html#</guid>
<pubDate>Options +IndexesMon, 11 Sep 2023 21:15:20 +0200</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[

]]></description>
</item>






</channel>
</rss>

